Education College Records (Preliminary Inventory) 1911-1958
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections (MASC)
- General Office Records, including correspondence, budgets, course materials, and conference proceedings, 1911-1958; 1
  - Z 40 (No Year) (Box 12)
  - Geiger, Virgil 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Alpha 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session Driver Education 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session Publicity 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session 1947 (Box 12)
  - State Dept. of Pub. Inst. 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Courses, Schedules 1948 (Box 12)
  - Budget 1946 (Box 12)
  - Conferences, Camps, Workshops, ect. 1947 (Box 12)
  - Belch, Elinor Louise 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Payroll 1949 (Box 12)
  - Payroll – Past 1948 (Box 12)
  - Fees 1948 (Box 12)
  - Finances, Cost Accounting, ect. 1948 (Box 12)
  - Housing 1948 (Box 12)
  - Enrollment 1948 (Box 12)
  - Driver Education 1948 (Box 12)
  - Recreation, Entertainment 1948 (Box 12)
  - Staff – 1948-1950 (Box 12)
  - Staff – Visiting Faculty 1949 (Box 12)
  - Staff Applications – Inactive 1948 (Box 12)
  - Staff Offers 1947 (Box 12)
  - Travel Organizations and Vouchers 1946 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session – Evergreen Stories – 1st Ea. 1946 (Box 12)
  - I 1946 (Box 12)
  - Summer School Correspondence 1946 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session Salaries 1947 (Box 12)
  - Applications for Chisholm’s Job -1945 (Box 12)
  - Book Advertisements 1945 (Box 12)
  - Atlanta Ga. 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session 1947 – Actual Office (Box 12)
  - School Administrators Conference 1946 (Box 12)
  - Budget – April 1944-March 1945 (Box 12)
  - Delinquent List ‘46 (Box 12)
  - State Dept. of Education 1946 (Box 12)
  - Supervision Conference for Summer 1947 (Box 12)
  - Public Affairs 1947 (Box 12)
  - Payroll 1947 (Box 12)
  - Course Schedule 1947 (Box 13)
  - President’s Committees – Reports to and From 1947 (Box 13)
  - Quarterly Budget – July 1 to Sept 31, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Budget-April 1945 – March 1946 (Box 13)
  - Catalog (Bulletin) 1947 (Box 13)
  - Catalog Changes 1947 (Box 13)
  - Cadet Teachers 1944-1946 (Box 13)
  - 1948 Summer Session Course Additions and Changes (Box 13)
  - Placement Policy Committee 1946 (Box 13)
  - President Compton – Changes in Salary 1946 (Box 13)
  - Summer Session Course Additions 1948 (Box 13)
  - President Compton – Resignations 1946 (Box 13)
  - Enrollments 1940, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Wash. Education Assn. 1946 (Box 13)
  - Counseling and Registration 1946 (Box 13)
  - Lowell Poore Ed 173. 7/19/48 (Box 13)
  - Summer Session Grade Reports (No Year) (Box 13)
  - Committee to Survey Patterns of Teaching Training Inst. 1944 (Box 13)
  - Practice Teaching Material 1946-47 (Box 13)
  - President Compton – Appointments 1947 (Box 13)
  - President’s Office 1946 (Box 13)
  - Students enrolled in Sch. of Educ. Starting 1942-43 (Box 13)
  - Curriculum and Catalog Committee Integrated Courses 1945 (Box 13)
  - Instructors Programs 1948 (Box 13)
  - Conservation Workshop 1947 (Box 13)
  - Graduate School 1948 (Box 13)
  - Committees – Steering 1948 (Box 13)
  - Committees – Improvments of Instruction 1948 (Box 13)
  - Fellowships 1949-1950 (Box 13)
  - Hopkins Office 1948 (Box 13)
  - Comptroller 1948 (Box 13)
  - Community College Service 1948 (Box 13)
  - Library 1947 (Box 13)
  - Junior College 1948 (Box 13)
  - Inquires – Prospective Students 1948 (Box 13)
  - Inquires – General, Policy, etc. 1948 (Box 13)
  - In-Service – Courses, Training 1948 (Box 13)
  - Compton – President’s Office (Box 13)
  - Recommendations 1946 (Box 13)
  - Placement Bureau 1948 (Box 13)
  - Policy – WSC 1948 (Box 13)
  - Register – 1948 (Box 13)
  - Registration 1947 (Box 13)
  - Schedules – Second Semester 1947 (Box 13)
  - Schedules – First Semester 1947 (Box 13)
  - Scholarship – PTA 1949 (Box 13)
  - Staff – Memos, Minutes 1948 (Box 13)
  - Budget – Biennium, 1947-‘49 (Box 13)
  - Staff – Part-time, Time-slip, ect. 1948 (Box 13)
  - Budget 1948-49 (Box 14)
  - Budget – Past 1948 (Box 14)
  - Catalog Changes 1949 (Box 14)
  - Catalog Changes 1948 (Box 14)
  - Staff – Appointments and Resignations 1946 – Aug 1950 (Box 14)
  - PTA Scholarships 1950 (Box 14)
  - Scholarships – PTA Inquires and Correspondence 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - Staff-Memos and Minutes 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - Teacher Education 1950 (Box 14)
  - Veterans Administration 1847-1950 (Box 14)
  - Student Teaching 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - Staff Recommendations for Promotion, Policy, Retirement, Tenure 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - Staff-W.S.C. Resident Instructional 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - Staff – Needs 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - Staff-Instructor’s Programs 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - Eastern Washington College of Education up to 1949 (Box 14)
  - AATCE Prior to Sept 1951 (Box 14)
  - A – Correspondence 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - C Correspondence 1946-9/1/50 (Box 14)
  - B Correspondences 1946 – Sept 1, 1950 (Box 14)
  - D Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 14)
  - E – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 14)
  - F – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 14)
  - G – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - H – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - Art Education (Box 15)
  - I – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - J – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - K – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - L – Correspondence to 9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - Office Correspondence Ma-Mc 1947-9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - Me-Mi Correspondence 1947-9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - Mo-My Correspondence Sept 1, 1951 (Box 15)
  - N – Correspondence 1946-9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - O – Correspondence 1947-9/1/50 (Box 15)
  - Agricultural Education 1946-1950 (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia Curr. Mat’s 1945 (Box 15)
  - State Dept. of Public Inst. 1949 (Box 15)
  - Curriculum Development 1947Research 1948 (Box 15)
  - Venn, Grant 1950 (Box 15)
  - Spokane 1949 (Box 15)
  - Guidance 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Educational Psychology 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Elementary Education 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Budget Statements 1950 (Box 15)
  - Book Store 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - Certificates 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Child Development Program Committee 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Carnagie Project – Closed 1947-49 (Box 15)
  - Compton – President’s Office 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds – Dead File – To Dec, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Bulletins – Campus 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Catalogs Bulletins – 1950 (Box 15)
  - Committees – Educational Policies – up through 1950 (Box 15)
  - Civilian Defense Prior to Jan. 1952 (Box 15)
  - Committees Administrative Council – up to Jan. 1950 (Box 15)
  - Committees – Misc. 1950 (Box 15)
  - Graduate Studies Committee up to December 1950 (Box 15)
  - Community College Service up to Dec. 1950 (Box 15)
  - Equipment 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - General Certificate 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - Graduate School 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - Hopkin’s Office 1944-1950 (Box 16)
  - Improvement of Instr. Committee 1950 (Box 16)
  - Interdepartmental Communications 1950 (Box 16)
  - Inquiries – General, Policy, etc. 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - Junior Collage 1947-1950 (Box 16)
  - KWSC 1947-50 (Box 16)
  - Library 1947-50 (Box 16)
  - Military Information 1947-50 (Box 16)
  - Non-Faculty Personnel 1949-50 (Box 16)
  - Placement Bureau 1946-57 (Box 16)
  - Phi Delta Kappa 1948-50 (Box 16)
  - Register 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - Recommendations 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - Policy – WSC 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - Schedule – 1st Semester, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - Schedule – 2nd Semester, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - Scholarship – General Information 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - Scholarship – Chi Omega 1948-50 (Box 16)
  - Applications Feb 1948 (Box 16)
  - Schedule – 1st Semester 1948-49 (Box 16)
  - Saturday Classes 1949 (Box 16)
  - Schedule – 2nd Semester 1948-49 (Box 16)
  - Reguicitians Outstanding 1950 (Box 16)
  - Prospects Rejected – Papers Returned 1950 (Box 16)
  - Staff Applications – Active 1949 (Box 16)
  - Carmody, Harriett 1948 (Box 16)
  - Dule, Katherine 1949 (Box 16)
  - Special Methods, 1949 (Box 16)
  - Thorne, Thelma 1950 (Box 16)
  - Oviatt, Delmer T. 1950 (Box 16)
  - Ohlsen, Merle M. 1950 (Box 16)
  - Placement Bureaus 1950 (Box 16)
  - Staff Offers – 1950 (Box 16)
  - Staff Applications – Closed 1950 (Box 16)
  - Staff Applications – 1950 (Box 16)
  - Fellowships 1950 (Box 16)
  - Elementary Education 1950 (Box 17)
  - Guidance 1949 (Box 17)
  - Comptroller 1949 (Box 17)
  - Staff – Appointments and Resignations 1946 (Box 17)
  - Travel Expense Vouchers – Old 1948 (Box 17)
  - Enrollment 1949 (Box 17)
  - Evergreen 1947 (Box 17)
  - Conferences, Camps, Workshops, ect. 1949 (Box 17)
  - Curriculum 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - Education 193 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - Child Development 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - Life Certificates – 1949 (Box 17)
  - School of Education 1948 – Spring (Box 17)
  - Education (no year) (Box 17)
  - Lange, Phil 1947 (Box 17)
  - Tall, Lewis R. 1947 (Box 17)
  - Dr. H. Robert Otness 1946 (Box 17)
  - Otness, Dr. Herman R. (permanent file) (no year) (Box 17)
  - Teaching Fellows 1947 (Box 17)
  - Institute for School Lunch Cooks 1946 (Box 17)
  - Schedules 1946 (Box 17)
  - Schedule 1945-1946 (Box 17)
  - Psychology Applications 1946 (Box 17)
  - Instructors in Psych. 1946 (Box 17)
  - Psychology Dept. 1946 (Box 17)
  - Prospective Students 1946 (Box 17)
  - Investigation of Courses, Schedules 1945 (Box 17)
  - State Department – Bigelow 1946 (Box 17)
  - Senate 1945 (Box 17)
  - Elementary 1949 (Box 17)
  - Certification 1948 (Box 17)
  - Scholarships PTA 1947 (Box 17)
  - Elem. Sch. Science Prof. folder 1947 (Box 17)
  - State Department of Education 1944 (Box 17)
  - Vocational Education – St. Dept., H.Ec, Agric. (Box 17)
  - State Board 1944 (Box 17)
  - Faculty Personal Questionaire 1946 (Box 17)
  - State Board Minutes 1943 (Box 17)
  - Ellensburg Conference Student Teaching 1947 (Box 17)
  - Elementary Committee on Instruction – Minutes at Meetings (no year) (Box 17)
  - Lee 1948 (Box 17)
  - Diary 1946 (Box 17)
  - Journal (no year) (Box 17)
  - Catalog Copy – Old 1949 (Box 17)
  - Staff – 1950 (Box 17)
  - Staff Offers, Prospects 1949 (Box 17)
  - General 1947 (Box 17)
  - Publicity 1949 (Box 17)
  - University of Washington 1948 (Box 17)
  - United States Office of Education 1948 (Box 17)
  - Yakima Area (No Year) (Box 17)
  - Washington Education Association 1948 (Box 17)
  - State Department of Public Instruction 1948 (Box 17)
  - State Board – Minutes 1948 (Box 18)
  - Richard Area 1948 (Box 18)
  - Strayer Report 1946 (Box 18)
  - King County 1949 (Box 18)
  - Committees – Conservation of Resources 1948 (Box 18)
  - National Association Colleges and Departments of Education 1947 (Box 18)
  - Chicago (No Year) (Box 18)
  - Bulletins – Printed Matter 1948 (Box 18)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teachers Education 1948 (Box 18)
  - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development 1948 (Box 18)
  - Committees – Educational Policies 1948 (Box 18)
  - Inter – Dept’l Requis. Old 1949 (Box 18)
  - General Courses 1947 (Box 18)
  - Travel Expense Vouchers 1947 (Box 18)
  - Visual Aids 1948 (Box 18)
  - Vocational Educational 1946 (Box 18)
  - Transcripts – Inquiring Students (Not Enrolled at WSC) 1948 (Box 18)
  - Travel – Authorizations 1948 (Box 18)
  - Staff – Schedules and Programs 1949 (Box 18)
  - Staff – Salaries 1948 (Box 18)
  - Student Teaching 1948 (Box 18)
  - 2710 Education Education – 2960 Summer Session 1949 (Box 18)
  - Social Studies 1941 (Box 18)
  - A.A.C.T.A. – Alberta Canada – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Lumber – up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Professional Services Rendered – up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Subscription Fees and Assoc. Dues up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Service Contracts and Repair Bills up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Travel Tickets up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Test and Books up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Equipment C-F up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Equipment G-M up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Equipment – Mongomery Ward up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Equipment N-R up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Student Bookstore up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Off Campus Requisitions – Rejected up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Lee Allen HDWE, American ReedCraft Cor., Brodhead Garret Co. 1950 (Box 18)
  - Utilities and Construction up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Visual Aids up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Central Stores up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Printing Department up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Duplicating and Mailing up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Building and Grounds up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Photographic Lab up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Advertisement up to Sept 1, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Pa-Pe Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Pi-Py Correspondence 9-1-50 (Box 19)
  - Ra-Ri Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Ro-Ry Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Sti-Sy Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Sn-Ste Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Se-Sm Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Sa-Sc Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - T Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - U Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Wa-Wi Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Wh-Wy Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - XYZ Correspondence Sept 1, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Lee – Personal 1952 (Box 19)
  - “The Child” – Revision Personal 1952 (Box 19)
  - Lee – Publishers – Personal 1951 (Box 19)
  - Travel Requests – Personal 1949 (Box 19)
  - State Board Minutes Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Certification – Special Cases – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Placement Bureau – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Committees – President’s Advisory Inter-Institutional Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Travel Safety – Committee – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Columbia Basin – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - American Assoc. School Administrators – Prior to Sept 1950 (Box 19)
  - Commitments – 1951 Summer Session – Visiting Staff (Box 19)
  - A.A. Cleveland Summer Conference Workshop for Public School Counselors 1950 (Box 19)
  - A Regional Program to Improve School Administration in the Pacific Northwest (No Year) (Box 19)
  - Elementary School Principals Letters, 1950-1951 (Box 19)
  - SS Correspondence 1951 (Box 19)
  - Evergreen 1951 (Box 19)
  - Recreation, Entertainment 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Agriculture 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Biological Science 1951 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Business Administration and Econ 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Chemistry 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Education 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – English and Journalism (no year) (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Engineer and Mining 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Fine Arts 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Foreign Languages (no year) (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Geology and Geography (no year) (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – History (no year) (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Home Ec. 1951 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Industrial Arts 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Library Sciences 1951 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session – Mathematics (no year) (Box 19)
  - Music 1950 (Box 19)
  - Physical Education (no year) (Box 19)
  - Political Science (no year) (Box 19)
  - Psychology 1950 (Box 19)
  - Summer Sessions 1950 (Box 20)
  - Payroll 1950 (Box 20)
  - Evergreen Girls State 1950 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session Information Sheet 1950 (Box 20)
  - Inquiries – Summer School 1950 (Box 20)
  - Demonstration Classes 1949 (Box 20)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Scholarship 1951 (Box 20)
  - Fees 1950 (Box 20)
  - Finances, Cost Accounting, Etc. (Box 20)
  - Small Classes 1951 (Box 20)
  - Housing 1950 (Box 20)
  - Courses, Schedules 1950 (Box 20)
  - Conferences, Camps, Workshops, Etc 1951 (Box 20)
  - Family Life Conference 1949 (Box 20)
  - Driver Education 1951 (Box 20)
  - Mailing List – Summer Session Bulletin 1951 (Box 20)
  - Catalog Material 1950 (Box 20)
  - General – 1951 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session Bulletin 1951 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session 1951 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Misc. 1951 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Misc. 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Expense Vouchers 1949 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – David E. Willis 1949 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – David E. Willis 1949 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – E.M. Webb 1949 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – E.M. Webb 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Grant Venn 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Lealand D. Stier 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Grant Venn 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Lealand D. Stier 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Winfred McCredy 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Gordon McClosky 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Gordon McClosky 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – S.V. Martorana 1950 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – S.V. Martorana 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Oscar Loreen 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Oscar Loreen 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Dorric Mae Lee 1950 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Norman Lange 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Zeno B Katterle 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Zeno B Katterle 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – C.E. Humes 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – C.E. Humes 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Louise Gentry 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Louise Gentry 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Requests – Virgil A. Geiger (No Year) (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Virgil A. Geiger 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Vouchers – Dorthy Cook 1952 (Box 20)
  - Travel Request Dorthy Cook 1949 (Box 20)
  - 1952 SS Workshops (Box 20)
  - Summer Session 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session Schedule 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – Staff Committees 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session Schedule 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – Staff Applications 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – Room Scheduling 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – Publicity 1951 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – Publicity 1952 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session – New Course Petitions 1952 (Box 21)
  - Instructor’s Programs 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – High School Summer Camp 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – General 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Driver Education 1952 (Box 21)
  - 1952 SS Committees (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Departmental Agreements 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Departmental Approvals 1952 (Box 21)
  - Demonstration Class 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Crippled Children 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Courses to be added 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session Catalog 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Budget – Visiting Staff 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session Activities 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Application Forms 1952 (Box 21)
  - Forms, Lists, ect. 1952 (Box 21)
  - Ideas – 55 1949 (Box 21)
  - Curriculum Course – WSC 1942 (Box 21)
  - Curriculum Opinions on Revision 1937 (Box 21)
  - Curriculum 1963 (Box 21)
  - Ed 243 1939 (Box 21)
  - Poffenroth Lydia (No Year) (Box 21)
  - Aviation 1942 (Box 21)
  - Curriculum Class 1941 Correspondence (Box 21)
  - Curriculum Class 1942 (Box 21)
  - Education 165 1943 (Box 21)
  - Education 160 1940 (Box 21)
  - Textbook Material 1941 (Box 21)
  - Supervision – Case Study of Grog. 1946 (Box 21)
  - American Assn. for Teacher Education – Bulletins and Correspondence 1954-56 (Box 21)
  - State Board of Education 1954-55 (Box 21)
  - State Board of Education Minutes Sept. 1953-Sept. 1954 (Box 21)
  - State Board Minutes Sept. 1952 – Sept. 1953 (Box 21)
  - State Board Minutes Sept. 1951 to Date (Box 21)
  - Faculty Book Orders – Summer Session 1956 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session – Correspondence 1955-56 and Memorandum (Box 21)
  - Summer Session Correspondence and Miscellaneous 1956 (Box 22)
  - Summer Session – Bookmen’s Display 1956 (Box 22)
  - Driver Education Training 1955 (Box 22)
  - Staff Committee to Study Sept. Experience (Box 22)
  - State Department – Pearl Wanamaker 1954-1955 (Box 22)
  - State Department – Miscellaneous 1954-1955 (Box 22)
  - State Department – Wendell Allen 1954-55 (Box 22)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - State Board of Education 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - State Department – Miscellaneous 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - Follow-up Trips 1954-55 and 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - State Department – Pearl Wanamaker 1955-1956 (Box 22)
  - State Department Teacher Education Committee Meeting March 22-23, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Washington Education Association 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - Annual Budget 1952-53 (Box 22)
  - Annual Budget 1951-52 (Box 22)
  - Annual Budget 1950-51 (Box 22)
  - Elementary Educ. Materials for Dean’s Class 1950 (Box 22)
  - Education 187, 1951 (Box 22)
  - Education 184 (no year) (Box 22)
  - Examinations – Ed 140 – Ed 181 (no year) (Box 22)
  - Master’s Theses – Dean Lee’s Desk Drawer 1952 (Box 22)
  - Elem. Prin. 1950 (Box 22)
  - Principal’s Book 1951 (Box 22)
  - Committees – Teacher Education 1947 (Box 22)
  - Annual Budget 1949-50 (Box 22)
  - Biennial Budget 1951-53 (Box 22)
  - Biennial Budget 1953-55 (Box 22)
  - Biennial Budget 1949-51 (Box 22)
  - Graduate School 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - Graduate School 1951-52 (Box 22)
  - 2710 – Education – 3 Operations – Complete, 1955-56 – Interdepartmental (Box 22)
  - 2710 – Education – 4 Equipmental – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2710 – Education – 6 Time Slip – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2710 – Education – 9 Dean’s Resource – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2710 – Education - 8 Accounts Receivable – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2711 – Student Teaching – 3 Operations – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2721 – Ag Education – 3 Operations – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2960 – Summer Session – 2 Travel – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - 2960 – Summer Session – 3 Operations – Complete, 1955-56 (Box 22)
  - Non – Faculty Personnel and Time Slips – Sept. 1953 – Sept. 1954 (Box 22)
  - Staff Appointments 1953-1954 (Box 22)
  - Staff – Appointments and Resignations 1952-1953 (Box 22)
  - Staff – Recommendations for Promotions, Policy, Retirements, Tenure 1952-1953 (Box 22)
  - President’s Office Sept. 1952 – Sept. 1953 – S.T. Stephenson (Box 22)
  - Travel Vouchers – School of Education Staff 1955-56 (Box 23)
  - President’s Office Sept. 1953 – Sept. 1954 – C. Clement French (Box 23)
  - AACTE – Correspondence, 56-57 (Box 23)
  - AACTE – Bulletins, 1956-57 (Box 23)
  - AACTE – Committee on Statements of Position and Resolutions – Correspondence 1957 (Box 23)
  - American Association of School Administration – Bulletins, 1956-58 (Box 23)
  - AASA – Martin Essex for President 1957-58 (Box 23)
  - Connell School District 1957 (Box 23)
  - 2nd Drawer – Central Valley School District 1957 (Box 23)
  - Colfax Schools 1954 (Box 23)
  - Conferences and Conventions 1955-56 and 1956-57 (Box 23)
  - Freeman, Roger – Reports and Correspondence 1953 (Box 23)
  - Ground Observer Corps Seminar November 12-13 1956 (Box 23)
  - Pakinstan Project – Requisitions 1956 (Box 23)
  - Pakinstan – Reports 1956 (Box 23)
  - Pakinstan – General Correspondence Through November, 1956 (Box 23)
  - American Assoc. of Colleges for Teacher Training – Reports, Budgets, Minutes – Before Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - American Assoc. of Colleges for Teacher Training – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - State Department – Wendell Allen – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - State Department – Boydie Rich – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - State Department – Pearl Wanamaker – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - State Department of Public Instr. – Misc. – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - Sunnyside Schools – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - U.S. Dept. of Educ. Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - University of Washington Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - Wash. Educ. Association – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)
  - PTA – Prior to Sept. 1950 (Box 23)